

Personal details:



Belarus, Minsk



+375(29)644-13-75



+375(29)644-13-75



@suv_la



dmitry-luk



d.fibber@gmail.com



Additional activities

Languages:

English:

- Intermediate
- Pre-Intermediate (Speaking)

Belarusian: Native Russian: Native

Courses:

IT-Academy - Functional testing (Professional course)
Finished: September 2022
First place in the defense of the final project.

My Freedom - Software testing (Base course)

Finished: August 2021.

Moonlight language school

Learning English 2021-current

Additional courses:

- Artsiom Rusau Video course on YouTube.
- Aleksey Marshal Video course on YouTube.

Literature:

- **Svyatoslav Kulikov** Software Testing Base Course
- Roman Savin Testing dot com

Interests:

- · New technologies
- Photoshop
- English
- Workout
- Fishing

Dmitry Luk

Junior QA Engineer

Completed a course in a software testing (manual). Can work in Jira, Xray, TestRail, have strong basic knowledge of SQL. I have experience in web application testing. Want to use my knowledge for real business projects and be useful for your company.

Hard skills:

- Operating systems: Windows
- Basic knowledge: HTML, CSS, JSON, XML, SQL
- · Bug tracking system: Jira
- Tools: Postman, SoapUI, TestRail, Xray, Chrome DevTools, Selenium IDE, Confluence, Charles, GITHUB
- Basic knowledge: Quality assurance, quality control, testing, SDLC, STLC, defect lifecycle, types, methods and levels of testing
- Basic test-design techniques, types of test documentation: test plan, check list, acceptance sheet, test survey, test-cases, bug reports, TRR
- QA responsibilities: functional/non-functional testing, requirements testing, GUI testing, new feature testing, smoke/critical path/extended testing, regression testing, API-testing

Examples test documentation creation and supporting on project:

Test plan Check-list Test-cases TRR Bug reporting

Work experience:

02.03.2015 – 15.02.2019 IronTradePlus LTD, position: head of sales department

- Created an application for automatic calculation of components based on EXCEL, which accelerated the processing of orders
- Promoted the site to the top 5 companies on Deal.by platform
- SEO company website promotion, content creation and posting/publishing

01.02.2013 – 13.02.2015 GospodarExport LTD, position: founder of the company

08.02.2010 – 20.12.2012 GosMetall LTD, position: sales Specialist 01.04.2009 – 30.07.2010 Gorstroymontazh LTD, position: deputy director for commercial activities

01.07.2008 – 01.04.2009 Gorstroymontazh LTD, position: leading specialist of the sales department

Proficiency:

- Conclusion of contracts for the supply of products with factories
- Conclusion of sales contracts with buyers
- Preparation of tender documents and participation, communication with the customer

Education:

01.09.2003 - 30 .06.2008 International Sakharov Environmental University, full-time, budget

Soft skills:

- Responsibility
- Communicability
- · Ability to work in a team
- Attentive to the details
- High learning ability
- Creativity